Dare to believe
The Magician's Elephant is a animation, adventure,
family film directed by Wendy Rogers.
Peter is searching for his long-lost sister when he crosses
paths with a fortune teller in the market square.
His only question is: is his sister still alive?
The answer, that he must find a mysterious elephant and the magician who will conjure it, sets Peter off on a
journey to complete three seemingly impossible tasks that will change the face of his town forever.
Peter (voice), played by Noah Jupe.
Vilna Lutz (voice), played by Mandy Patinkin.
Leo Matienne (voice), played by Brian Tyree Henry.
Narrator / Fortune Teller (voice), played by Natasia Demetriou.
Gloria Matienne (voice), played by Sian Clifford.
Magician (voice), played by Benedict Wong.
The Magician's Elephant is a 2023 animated fantasy adventure film directed by
Wendy Rogers, written by Martin Hynes and produced by Julia Pistor.
Based on the 2009 novel by Kate DiCamillo, the film features the voices of Noah Jupe, Mandy
Patinkin, Natasia Demetriou, Benedict Wong, Miranda Richardson and Aasif Mandvi.
Animated by Animal Logic, the film was distributed by
Netflix and released on March 17, 2023.
The tone is lighthearted.